Oh prom. That beautiful time of the year
哦，舞会期。一年中最美好的时光
that all you can hear in the hallways is.
在学校走廊上听到的一切都是。
Are you going to prom? or
你要去舞会吗？ 或
you think she's gonna say yes, and of course every girl
你觉得她会答应是嘛，当然还有每个女孩
is gonna be talking about one thing.
都会讨论一件事。
-So what are you gonna wear? -I think something pink, i don't know.
-你舞会穿啥？ -不知啊，粉红一点吧。
These guys don't even go to our school.
这些人甚至不是本校的。
Last but not least, the ones who hate prom.
还有最后一种，讨厌舞会的人。
-Can we not go to prom? -Over it!
-别去舞会了，行不？ -没问题，早受够了！
-You wanna go to prom with me? -Yes. -YES
-你能和我一起参加舞会吗？ -没问题。 -太棒了。
Yes,yess,yes,yeahhh..
可以的..
-Hey, you wanna go to prom with me? -Oh my god yes.
-嘿，你能和我一起参加舞会吗？ -天呐，我愿意。
Surprise!!
惊喜！！
Guys, it's the wrong girl.
老铁，弄错女孩了。
Hey, don't take this the wrong way, but I heard one of the guys
嘿，别理解错了，但我听到有个男孩
says they want to take a goth girl to prom.
说想带一个哥特女孩去舞会。
-Shut up, -Yeah. -Whoo?
-可闭嘴吧你。 -真的。 -是谁？
I think it's that guy.
我想是那个货。
Nooo, that can't happen, i can't go to prom, let's go, let's go goo
不行啊，我不会去舞会的，跑吧。
WHAT!!
我去！！
Wwwait no nooo, i need to talk to you about prom.
等等等，我要跟你聊聊那个舞会。
Who? I don't want talk about it, i don't want go to prom with you.
谁要和你聊聊，我不想跟你去舞会。
I know, i don't wanna go to prom with you either.
我知道，我也不想跟你去舞会。
-Then why are you following me? -Well
-那你为啥追我？ -恩..
i want to take Electra to prom and
我想和伊莱克特拉一块去舞会，
i want you to help me take her.
希望你能帮帮我。
Oh, that's where you are pointing. Okay well, not my problem.
原来如此。明白了，但与我无关啊。
Whoa whoa wait please, i have to take her to prom.
哇哇，等等呗，我得和她一起去舞会啊。
-Uh-huh, so? -Mmm can you help me? -Oh no
-然后呢？ -恩.. 你能帮我吗？ -不能！
-or i'll take you. -Okay let's go.
-那我就带你去。-帮你了，走起。
-Yo, don't take this the wrong way. -What?
-老妹，别误会了。-什么？
-But i'll show you something. -Shut up! -I know, come here.
-我先给你看样东西。-几个意思！ -我懂，来这看。
YO..
看呐  ..
-Did you know about this? -Yeah.
-你知道这事吗？ -知道。
You're dead, like the squirrel in my room.
你死了，跟我房间的松鼠一样。
-Can you just answer? -Yes
-你能赶紧回答吗？ -可以
under one condition.
但有一个条件。
Anything.
啥条件都行。
-What condition? -Get closer. get closer. get closer..
-什么条件？ -靠近一点儿，近一点儿，近一点点儿。
I’m getting closer.
近一点个屁，滚。